She should be at the temple at this hour.
ينبغي أن تكون في المعبد في هذه السّاعة
The line to see the Lady Cleric is here.
طابور رؤية الكاهنة من هنا
Please have your ticket in hand.
سلّموا تذاكركم باليد رجاءً
Man, I feel alive again!
!أشعر بالحيوية من جديد
My body feels so much lighter.
أشعر أنّ جسدي صار خفيفاً
Looks like she's working hard again today. Hopefully not too hard.
يبدو أنّها تعمل بجدّ ثانية اليوم. آمل ألّا تُجهد نفسها
I believe there is.
يوجد على ما أعتقد
If we find a cleric who can exorcise evil...
...إذا وجدنا كاهنة تستطيع طرد الشرّ
But she rarely takes on jobs to remove curse-based skills.
لكنّها نادراً ما تقبل بأعمال إزالة مهارات تعتمد على لعنة
There may be some reason behind it,
،قد يكون هناك سبب ما وراء ذلك
but I'm her best friend, and she won't even tell me.
لكن أنا أعزّ صديقة لها، ومع ذلك لا تخبرني
Lady Cleric...
...سينسي
I'm taking a break.
سآخذ استراحة
I apologize, but please wait.
أعتذر، لكن انتظر رجاءً
Understood.
عُلم
Oh, whoops...
...بئساً
I seem to be out of energy.
يبدو أنّ طاقتي نفدت
It appears as though you're working too hard, Lady Cleric.
يبدو أنّكِ تُتعبين نفسكِ كثيراً يا سيّدتي الكاهنة
Oh, it's you, Lola.
هذه أنتِ يا لولا
That's quite the greeting for someone who's worried about you.
أي تحيّة هي هذه لشخص قلق عليكِ
I apologize.
أعتذر
So what's the very capable receptionist from the guild doing here today?
حسناً، ما الذي تفعله موظّفة الاستقبال المُؤهّلة من النّقابة هنا اليوم؟
I hate to ask this when I know you're tired,
،لم أتمنّ أن أطلب منكِ وأنتِ مُتعبة
but I needed to discuss something important with you.
لكن أردتُ مناقشة شيء مهمّ معكِ
Today's the day that Lola is going to introduce us to this cleric.
اليوم هو اليوم الذي ستعرِّفنا فيه لولا على هذه الكاهنة
I had some time before we were supposed to meet up,
،كان لديّ بعض الوقت قبل موعد لقائنا
so I decided to get some advice from my master.
لذا قرّرتُ أخذ نصيحة ما من مُعلّمتي
"Hidden dungeon only I can enter!
!الدّيماس الخفيّ الذي لا يستطيع دخوله سواي"
Let me train in secret to become the strongest in the world!"
"!دعيني أتدرّب سرّاً لأصبح الأقوى في العالم
#04 "The Untainted Cleric"
"الحلقة 4  "الكاهنة النقيّة
M-Master?
مـ-معلّمة؟
Are you mad about something?
هل هناك ما يُغضبكِ؟
Well, you haven't come see me at all!
!لأنّك لم تأتِ لرؤيتي إطلاقاً
I feel like it's been about two weeks.
أشعر وكأنّه مضى أسبوعان
S-Sorry about that!
!آ-آسف بشأن ذلك
I meant to come sooner,
،قصدتُ المجيء أبكر
but I ran into a little problem.
لكن واجهتُ مشكلة بسيطة
I see. A duke's daughter with a curse.
هكذا إذاً. ابنة دوق مُصابة بلعنة
Yes.
أجل
If it's a curse-based skill, it might have to do with her family.
إنّها مهارة تستند إلى لعنة، وقد يكون لها علاقة بعائلتها
Her family? You mean something to do with her ancestors?
عائلتها؟ تقصدين شيئاً له علاقة بأسلافها؟
Yeah, it happens all the time!
!أجل، يحدث هذا طوال الوقت
There's a skill to curse one's descendants.
هناك مهارة تلعن سُلالة أحدهم
But that's...
...لكن هذا
You'll need over 10,000 LP to Get Creative enough to create the skill to undo it.
ستحتاج لأكثر من 10.000 نقطة حياة لاستخدام الإبداع وخلق مهارة تُبطلها
It's probably best if you let that cleric girl handle it.
غالباً من الأفضل أن تدع تلك الكاهنة تتولّى ذلك
Right. That's what I plan on doing, but...
...حسناً. هذا ما أنوي فعله، لكن
I wonder what the Lady Cleric is like.
أتساءل ما هي طبيعة تلك السيّدة الكاهنة
If she has the skill to exorcise things, she's probably at least part elf.
إذا كان لديها مهارة طرد الأشياء، فجزء منها إيلف غالباً
An elf, huh?
إيلف؟
You don't see them very often.
نادراً ما نرى هذا النوع
It's great to fulfill some of your desires with other species.
من الرّائع أن ترضي رغباتك مع أنواع أخرى
You'll get lots of extra LP with them!
!ستحصد كثيراً من نقاط الحياة بواسطتهم
What?!
!ماذا؟
You gotta go for the glory!
!استمتع بأيّام مجيدة
Wh-What are you—
—ما-ما الذي
S-So, Master, what would you do to earn about 10,000 LP?
إ-إذاً يا معلّمة، ماذا أفعل لأكسب حوالي 10.000 نقطة حياة؟
Oh, in my case... Here. I'll whisper it to you.
في حالتي... اقترب. سأهمس في أذنك
First...
...أولاً
...to get their body extra sensitive...
...لتجعل جسدهن يتحسّس زيادة عن اللّزوم
...tie down their...
...قم بربط
...and while they're...
...وأثناء ذلك...
Then you'll have 10,000 LP in no time!
!حينئذ ستحصد 10.000 نقطة حياة فوراً
Jeez, I'm kidding. You're so cute, Noir.
تبّاً، أنا أمزح. أنت ظريف جدّاً يا نورو
Sh-She's totally messing with me...
...إ-إنها تعبث معي
You probably won't be able to get 10,000 that quickly,
غالباً لن تتمكّن من حصد 10.000 نقطة حياة بسرعة
but I can teach you a skill that'll be super useful in gaining LP.
لكن سأعلّمك مهارة نافعة جداً في كسب نقاط حياة
Really? That'll be great!
!حقّاً؟ سيكون هذا رائعاً
Okay! Let your awesome master Olivia fill you in on the deets.
حسناً! دع معلّمتك الرّائعة أوليفيا !تُطلعك على التّفاصيل
Thank you!
!شكراً لك
And now, for those deets...
...والآن، بالنسبة لتلك التّفاصيل
You'll get the best bang for your buck! This forbidden skill is...
...ستحظى بأفضل صفقة لك! هذه المهارة المُحرّمة هي
Lucky Lecher
الشّهواني المحظوظ
It only takes a measly 300 LP to get, but it's effective as hell!
تتطلّب فقط 300 نقطة حياة للحصول !عليها، لكنّها فعّالة جدّاً
Only takes 300 LP to get!
!تحتاج 300 نقطة حياة فقط للحصول عليها
You'll have some indescribable experiences!
!ستكتسب خبرة لا تُوصف
Get Creative to make Lucky Lecher!
!استخدام إبداع لصنع الشهوانيّ المحظوظ
Noir Stardia   Lv.35 LP.2270
نورو ستارجيا مستوى 35  النقاط 2270
Skills [Great Sage] [Get Creative] [Editor] [Bestow] Skills [LP Conversion] [Stone Bullet] [Discerning Eye] Skills [Headache Immunity] [Pocket Dimension (Grade C)] Skills [Improved Back Step] [Passive Defense] Skills [Shoulder Rub] [Lucky Lecher]
[الحكيم العظيم] [الإبداع] [المُعدّل] [منح] [تحويل نقاط الحياة] [رصاصة الحجر] [العين الثّاقبة] [مناعة ضدّ الصُّداع] [البُعد الجيبيّ الدرجة ج] [الخطوة الخلفيّة المُحسّنة] [الدّفاع السلبيّ] [فرك الكتف] [الشّهواني المحظوظ]
Noir Stardia   Lv.35 LP.1970
المهارات
Noir! Took you long enough!
!نورو! تأخّرت
The Lady Cleric and Lola are gonna show up soon!
!ستأتي السيّدة الكاهنة ولولا قريباً
Whoops, sorry!
!بئساً، آسف
Th-That Time I Faceplanted into Slime Boobs.
ذ-ذلك الوقت الذي اصطدمتُ فيه بصدر هُلامي
No!
!لا
Damn, my luck just won't stop!
!تبّاً، حظّي لا يتوقّف
This is how effective Lucky Lecher is?
أهذا تأثير مهارة شهوانيّ محظوظ؟
Buh-ling!
!هـ-هذه المهارة مذهلة
You're the best, Master.
أنتِ الأفضل يا معلّمة
But this is going to affect my life.
لكن سيؤثّر هذا على حياتي
I just need to use Editor to tinker with it a bit.
عليّ أن أستخدم مُعدّل لأعدّلها قليلاً
Lucky Lecher.
الشّهواني المحظوظ
Causes erotic situations to occur
تسبّب مواقف جنسيّة
Causes erotic situations to occur with nearby members of the opposite sex.
تُسبّب مواقف جنسيّة مع الأشخاص القريبين من الجنس المُغاير
with nearby members of the opposite sex.
مع الأشخاص القريبين من الجنس المُغاير
Just need to add "rarely."
عليّ إضافة "نادراً" فقط
Spent
تمّ إنفاق
with nearby members of the opposite sex.
مع الأشخاص القريبين من الجنس المُغاير
"rarely"
"نادراً"
As well as, "Skill will not trigger during serious situations."
"وكذلك، "مهارة لا تتفعّل أثناء الظروف الجدّية
Spent
تمّ إنفاق
"Skill will not trigger during serious situations."
"مهارة لا تتفعّل أثناء الظروف الجدّية"
Gotta make sure these only happen at the right time.
عليّ أن أحرص على ألّا تحدث هذه إلّا في الوقت المناسب
Hey! What are you smirking about?!
!لمَ تبتسم ابتسامة عريضة هكذا؟
I-I'm not!
!لـ-لستُ كذلك
You were totally staring at those other girls, too!
من الواضح أنّك كنت تحدّق بأولئك الفتيات أيضاً
That must be Noir.
لا بدّ وأنّه نورو
Noir, you doofus!
!نورو، أيّها الأحمق
He's pretty cute.
إنّه ظريف جدّاً
Just my type, actually.
نوعي المُفضّل في الواقع
Uh, Luna? What's that supposed to mean?!
!لونا؟ ما معنى هذا؟
Oh, Lola.
لولا
And...
...و
The Lady Cleric?
السيّدة الكاهنة؟
Sorry to keep you two waiting. This is...
...آسفة لو تأخرتُ عليكما. هذه
Luna Heela. It's nice to meet you two.
لونا هيلا. سررتُ بلقائكما
L-Likewise.
كـ-كذلك أنا
N-Nice to meet you.
س-سررتُ بلقائك
Yeah.
أجل
We've got reservations. We can talk there.
حجزتُ مكانًا لنا. يمكننا أن نتكلّم هناك
Her silky, smooth, silvery locks...
...خصلاتها الفضّية الملساء الحريريّة
Look at her from behind...
...أنظر إليها من الخلف
Her tight but perky butt...
...خلفيّتها النّحيلة والمليئة في نفس الوقت
Then her long, slim legs...
...وساقاها الطويلتان النّحيفتان
My only advantage over her is my boobs!
!أفضليّتي الوحيدة عليها هي صدري
I never should've let Noir meet her.
ما كان ينبغي أن أدع نورو يقابلها
Uh, Emma? Come on, let's go.
إيما؟ هيّا، لنذهب
Lola told me the basics.
أخبرتني لولا بمعلومات أساسيّة
So this person you want me to look at...
...إذاً الفتاة التي تريدني أن أعاينها هي
Miss Maria. She's the daughter of a duke.
ماريا-سان. ابنة دوق
So it's her.
إنّها هي إذاً
I've actually looked at her before...
...سبقَ وعاينتُها
But I declined lifting her curse.
لكن رفضتُ رفع لعنتها عنها
But why? Don't you have a skill to lift curses?
لكن لماذا؟ ألا تمتلكين مهارة رفع اللّعنات؟
Yes, I do. With no problems.
بلى، أملك. بلا أي مشاكل
But...
...لكن
I can't lift the Sixteenth Year Death Curse.
لا أستطيع رفع لعنة موت العام السّادس عشر
I can't save her.
لا أستطيع إنقاذها
How's Maria currently doing?
كيف حال ماريا حاليّاً؟
She doesn't even have a week to live.
لم يبقَ أمامها حتّى أسبوع للعيش
She suffers convulsions that pain her entire body.
تعاني من تشنُّجات تُؤلم كامل جسدها
Apparently, the intervals are getting shorter.
على ما يبدو، الفواصل الزمنيّة تقصُر
So her curse has progressed that far...
...إذاً تطوّرت لعنتها إلى هذا الحدّ
Luna, you don't need to feel responsible for this.
لونا، ليس عليك الشّعور بالمسؤوليّة تجاه هذا
You save dozens of people every day.
فأنتِ تنقذين العشرات كلّ يوم
That itself is an amazing feat.
هذا بحدّ ذاته إنجاز عظيم
It seems that Luna feels pretty responsible for this.
يبدو أنّ لونا تشعر بمسؤولية كبيرة تجاه هذا
Maybe she does have some kind of secret.
لعلّها تعرف سرّاً ما
Discerning Eye.
العين الثّاقبة
Species: Half-elf Age: 17 Occupation: Cleric/Adventurer Skills: [Magical Firearms (Grade B)] [Energizing Shot] Skills: [Healing Shot] [Cowardice] [Lift Curse]
لونا هيلا  المستوى 35
Yeah, she definitely has the Lift Curse skill...
النوع: نصف إيلف العمر: 17 المهنة: كاهنة\مُغامرة [الأسلحة النارية السحريّة درجة ب] [الطلقة المُنشّطة] [طلقة الشّفاء] [جُبن] [رفع اللّعنة]
Luna Heela   Lv.35
...أجل، لديها مهارة رفع اللّعنة بالتأكيد
Skill: Lift Curse Skill: Erases curse skills. However, the user's Skill: lifespan is reduced in proportion to Skill: the strength of the curse.
المهارة: رفع اللّعنة تزيل مهارات اللّعنة. غير أنّ عمر المُستخدم ينقص أكثر كلّما .كانت قوّة اللّعنة أكبر
Erases curse skills.
تزيل مهارات اللّعنة
However, the user's... lifespan is reduced?!
!غير أنّ عمر المُستخدم... ينقص؟
So when she lifts the curse, Luna's own lifespan is...
...إذاً عندما ترفع اللّعنة، فإنّ عمر لونا
Here it comes! This is a huge load!
!ثمّة حمولة ضخمة قادمة
Elves live far longer than humans.
الإيلف يعشن فترة أطول من البشر
But apparently, even so, Miss Maria's curse is so powerful
لكن يبدو أنّه رغم ذلك، لعنة ماريا-سان قويّة للغاية
that her lifespan can't cover it.
لدرجة أنّ عمرها لا يستطيع تغطية ذلك
Noir...
...نورو
Lead me to Miss Maria's home.
خذني إلى منزل ماريا-سان
I will lift her curse.
سأرفع لعنتها
B-But you just said you couldn't lift her curse.
لـ-لكن قلتِ للتو أنّكِ لا تستطيعين رفع لعنتها
Well...
...في الواقع
Emma, Lola.
إيما، لولا
Could you leave us for a bit?
هلّا تركتُمانا قليلاً؟
I'd like to talk to Luna in private.
أودّ أن أتكلّم مع لونا على انفراد
Sorry this is so sudden.
آسف لو فاجأتُكِ
I took a look at your stats with my skill.
ألقيتُ نظرة إلى إحصائيّاتكِ بمهارتي
If you cure Miss Maria, that means your life...
...إذا عالجتِ ماريا-سان، فهذا يعني أنّ حياتكِ
Stop! Don't say anymore!
!توقّف! لا تتكلّم أكثر
But—
—لكن
She's at death's door, isn't she?
إنّها على عتبة الموت، أليس كذلك؟
How could I possibly leave her alone knowing her life is at stake?
كيف لي أن أدعها وشأنها وأنا أعرف أنّ حياتها على المحكّ؟
I want to save people.
أريد إنقاذ الناس
Just like my mother would have done.
مثلما كانت أمّي لتفعل
My mother was also a cleric.
كانت أمّي كاهنة أيضاً
Even though she knew that her lifespan was at stake,
،رغم أنّها كانت تعلم أنّ عمرها كان على المحكّ
she continued lifting curses.
استمرّت في رفع اللّعنات
She kept her chipping away at her own lifespan to save those who were suffering.
ظلّت تضحّي بعمرها لإنقاذ أولئك الذين يعانون
And now, she's no longer with us.
والآن، لم تعد بيننا
But...
...لكن
I'm very proud of my mother.
أنا فخورة جدّاً بأمّي
Luna...
...لونا
And because I am my mother's daughter,
،ولأنّني ابنة أمّي
I want to use this power for others...
...أريد استخدام هذه القوّة لأجل الآخرين
The Hidden Dungeon Only I Can Enter.
الدّيماس الخفيّ الذي لا يستطيع دخوله سواي
There's trouble!
!هناك مشكلة
A wall collapsed! Someone help!
!سقط جدار! النّجدة
There's a child underneath!
!ثمّة طفل تحته
He's terribly injured!
!إنّه مُصاب بجروح بليغة
Hey, are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Hang in there!
!تماسك
W-We need to heal him immediately.
عـ-علينا مُعالجته فوراً
I wonder sometimes...
...أتساءل أحياناً
Why are we born into this world?
لماذا وُلِدنا في هذا العالم؟
I still don't know the answer to that.
ما زلتُ لا أعرف الإجابة على ذلك
It's all right.
لا بأس
I'm sure you'll find that answer someday.
أنا متأكّدة أنّك ستجد الإجابة يوماً ما
I guess you've already found yours, Luna.
أظنّكِ وجدتِ إجابتكِ بالفعل يا لونا
Yes.
أجل
I can save lives and bring about so many smiles.
يمكنني إنقاذ أرواح ورسم الكثير من البسمات في وجوه الآخرين
That is my mission!
!هذه مهمّتي
Healing Shot!
!طلقة الشّفاء
Thank goodness!
!هذا جيّد
Luna!
!لونا
W-Wow...
...مـ-مذهل
I guess your cleric title isn't just for show.
أعتقد أنّ لقب الكاهنة نلتِه عن استحقاق
Luna—
—لونا
Huh?! Luna?!
!ماذا؟! لونا؟
Are you... Huh?!
!هل أنتِ... ماذا؟
I don't wanna die
لا أريد أن أموت
I-I don't wanna die...
...لـ-لا أريد أن أموت
Curses are scary!
!اللّعنات مخيفة
Where did all of her bravery go?!
!أين ذهبتْ شجاعتها؟
Wait, could this be...
...لحظة، هل يُعقل أنّ هذه
[Cowardice]
[جُبن]
Skill
مهارة
Cowardice
جُبن
Depleting mana or receiving
استنزاف المانا أو تلقّي
intense attacks may make the
هجمات قويّة قد تجعل
user even more cowardly.
.المُستخدم أكثر جُبناً
Th-This probably sucks a lot.
هـ-هذا سيّئ للغاية
Luna!
!لونا
Oh, I knew it.
كما توقّعت
Luna's always like this.
لونا هكذا دوماً
Don't worry, she'll be awake in no time.
لا تقلق، ستستيقظ قريباً
Mommy...
...أمّي
Don't worry, Mommy's right here. Come on, now, up you go.
لا تقلقي، أمّكِ هنا. هيّا انهضي
I can't believe you saw that! Please just forget it!
!لا أصدّق أنكما رأيتما ذلك! انسيا ما رأيتماه
Please! Please! I beg of you!
!أرجوكما! أرجوكما! أتوسّل إليكما
Hey, it's okay...
...لا عليكِ
Yeah.
نعم
Now, let us proceed! Maria needs our help!
!حسناً، دعونا نمضي! ماريا بحاجة لمساعدتنا
Onward!
!إلى الأمام
B-But...
...لـ-لكن
Y-You don't need to worry about me...
...لـ-ليس عليك القلق بشأني
I'm not scared of... anything...
...لستُ خائفة... من أي شيء
Luna, let's figure out another way.
لونا، لنبحث عن طريقة أخرى
B-But why?
لـ-لكن لماذا؟
Your legs.
ساقاكِ
I-I just can't contain my excitement!
!لـ-لا أستطيع احتواء حماسي فحسب
But you said you were scared of curses.
لكن قلتِ أنّكِ تخشين اللّعنات
What? No way. Can't recall.
ماذا؟ مستحيل. لا أتذكّر ذلك
Bad Luna!
!هذا خطأ يا لونا
Just tell us the truth already.
أخبرينا بالحقيقة فحسب
You're scared, aren't you?
أنتِ خائفة، أليس كذلك؟
If I save Maria, it's very likely that I'm going to...
...إذا أنقذتُ ماريا، فمن المُرجّح أنّي سوف
die.
أموت
Just thinking about that is terrifying.
مجرّد التفكير في ذلك يُرعبني
I'm a failure as a cleric.
أنا فاشلة ككاهنة
You'll die if you lift a curse?
ستموتين إذا رفعتِ لعنة؟
You never told me that before!
!لم تخبريني بذلك من قبل
I'm sorry I didn't tell you. But I...
...آسفة لأنّي لم أخبركِ. لكنّني
So I've been hanging out with you this whole time
كنتُ أخرج معكِ طوال هذا الوقت إذاً
without realizing something that important.
دون إدراك شيء بهذه الأهمّية
N-No!
!لـ-لا
Some best friend! It pisses me off!
!أي صديقة عزيزة أنتِ؟! تستفزّينني
I'm so mad that I was so clueless.
أنا غاضبة جدّاً لأنّني كنتُ جاهلة
I'm sorry I didn't realize how much you were suffering.
آسفة لأنّني لم أدرك مدى معاناتكِ
You're always like this, Luna!
!أنتِ هكذا دوماً يا لونا
You always put others before yourself!
!دائماً ما تعطين الأولويّة للآخرين على نفسكِ
Lola...
...لولا
Rely on me... Please.
اعتمدي عليّ... أرجوكِ
Stupid Luna...
...لونا الحمقاء
Okay.
حسناً
Lola... Luna...
...لولا... لونا
There's something great about these two.
علاقتهما رائعة حقّاً
Sorry about all this.
آسفة بشأن كلّ هذا
You ended up witnessing such an embarrassing scene.
رأيتما في النّهاية مشهداً مُحرجاً
Oh, no. It was a feast for my eyes.
لا. كان ذلك مُمتعاً حقّاً
Er, I was very moved by you two.
أقصد تأثّرتُ بكما
But what should we do?
لكن ماذا ينبغي أن نفعل؟
If we try to save Miss Maria, then Luna will...
...إذا حاولنا إنقاذ ماريا-سان، فإنّ لونا سوف
Don't worry.
لا تقلقن
Things aren't completely hopeless yet.
ما زال هناك أمل
I'll be able to make this work without any casualties.
سأتمكّن من إنجاح هذا دون وقوع أي ضحايا
Earlier, I just gave it a shot, and took a look at Luna's Lift Curse skill.
قبل مدّة جرّبتُ وألقيتُ نظرة إلى مهارة رفع اللّعنة الخاصّة بلونا
[Lift Curse]
[رفع اللّعنة]
Erases curse skills.
تزيل مهارات اللّعنة
However, the user's lifespan is reduced in
غير أنّ عمر المُستخدم ينقص
proportion to the strength of the curse.
.كلّما كانت اللّعنة أقوى
I tried to get rid of the whole "lifespan is reduced" part, but...
...حاولتُ إزالة جزئيّة "العمر ينقص"، لكن
Uses
تُنفق
Necessary
لازمة
Finances
المال
rels
ريل
There's no way I can do 10,000 LP.
عمر المُستخدم .ينقص
Lifespan
العمر
User's lifespan is reduced.
من المستحيل أن أكسب 10.000 نقطة حياة
Then how about this?
ماذا عن هذه إذاً؟
[Lift Curse]
[رفع اللّعنة]
However, the user's lifespan is reduced in
غير أنّ عمر المُستخدم ينقص
Erases curse skills.
تزيل مهارات اللّعنة
proportion to the strength of the curse.
.كلّما كانت اللّعنة أقوى
I'll just change "lifespan" to "finances."
سأبدّل "عمر" بـ"مال" فحسب
However, the user's finances are reduced in
غير أنّ مال المُستخدم ينقص
Uses
تُنفق
Necessary
لازمة
Finances
المال
Perfect. This should work.
ممتاز. ينبغي لهذا أن ينجح
Lifespan
العمر
rels
ريل
User's finances are reduced.
مال المُستخدم يتناقص
There's a way to save Miss Maria without having to sacrifice Luna.
هناك طريقة لإنقاذ ماريا-سان دون الاضطرار للتضحية بلونا
Really, Noir?
أحقّاً يا نورو؟
Yup!
!أجل
But I don't have quite enough LP to use this skill...
لكن لا أملك ما يكفي من نقاط حياة ...لاستخدام هذه المهارة
LP?
نقاط حياة؟
Lacking
نقص
Delicious foods...
...طعام لذيذ
Making money and satisfying worldly desires...
...جني أموال وإشباع رغبات دنيويّة
And doing exciting things with attractive members of the opposite sex...
والقيام بأشياء مثيرة مع أعضاء جذّابين ...من الجنس المُغاير
Y-Yeah.
أ-أجل
I can't use my Get Creative or Editor skills without LP.
لا يمكنني استخدام مهارة الإبداع أو المُعدّل دون نقاط حياة
You know, you can't make an omelet without breaking a few eggs...
فمثلاً لا يمكنك إعداد عجّة دون كسر بضع بيوض
A-Anyway! Can you think of a way for me to get 2,000 more LP?
عـ-على أي حال! هل يمكنكن التّفكير بطريقة أحصل فيها على 2.000 نقطة حياة؟
And maybe something that'll increase Luna's finances.
أو طريقة ما تزيد من أموال لونا
You make it sound so easy.
تجعل الأمر يبدو سهلاً
I highly doubt there's anything that convenient.
أشكّ في وجود شيء مثالي إلى هذه الدّرجة
But there is.
بل يوجد
Huh?!
!ماذا؟
A certain noble holds the perfect event for this occasion every week.
ثمّة نبيل يقيم الفعاليّة المثاليّة لهذه المُناسبة أسبوعيّاً
The next time it will be held is this weekend,
،في المرّة المُقبلة ستُقام في نهاية هذا الأسبوع
so we'll make it just in time to lift the curse.
لذا سنصل في الوقت لرفع اللّعنة
What kind of event is it?
ما طبيعة الفعاليّة؟
It's called...
...تُدعى
It's called...?
تُدعى...؟
The Harem Pride Event!
!فعاليّة فخر النّساء
Sorry to keep you waiting, my dudes!
!آسف لو تأخّرت عليكم جميعاً
Tonight, another ten that I'm jealous of... I mean...
...اللّيلة، عشرة آخرون أغار منهم... أعني
We'll be meeting some reckless scoundrels who'll be showing off their hot girlfriends
سنلتقي ببعض الأوغاد الطّائشين الذين سيتباهون بخليلاتهم المُثيرات
for a chance at one million rels!
!للحصول على فرصة ربح مليون ريل
Unforgivable!
!هذا لا يُغتفر
Those lucky bastards!
!أولئك الأوغاد المحظوظون
Piss off!
!اغربوا عن وجوهنا
So vent all the stress you can at the sight of these shitty normies!
لذا صبّوا جام غضبكم على مشهد هؤلاء !العاديّين الأوغاد
Apparently, the host of this event has been betrayed by women countless times.
يبدو أنّ مُضيف هذه الفعاليّة خانته الكثير من النّساء
And the gentlemen who have gathered here have experienced something similar.
والرّجال الذين يتجمّعون هنا تعرّضوا لحادثة مشابهة
Most of them, apparently, don't have any lovers.
مُعظمهم على ما يبدو لا يملكون أي خليلة
Death to hot guys!
!الموت للوسيمين
Screw harems!
!تبّاً للنساء
Harems are unforgivable!
!لن نسامح النّساء
Th-This isn't a pride event... This is slander.
هـ-هذه ليست فعاليّة فخر... هذه فعاليّة افتراء
Are you ready, my dudes?
هل أنتم جاهزون يا قومي؟
Let the Harem Pride Event commence!
!لندع فعاليّة فخر النّساء تبدأ
I-I think I want to go home now...
...أ-أظنّني أريد الذهاب إلى المنزل الآن
Alice Theater
مسرح آليس
Big Brother...
...أخي
Y-You're back!
!عـ-عدت
What were you doing, Alice?
ماذا تفعلين يا آليس؟
Th-This is just... um...
...هـ-هذا فقط
I was just fixing your sheets!
!كنتُ أرتّب شرشفك
They seem messier than before.
يبدو فوضويّاً أكثر من السّابق
Don't worry. I'm just going to sleep in them as-is.
لا تقلقي. سأنام وهو على وضعه الحالي
Huh? Big Brother?
ماذا؟ أخي؟
I mean... we're siblings.
أعني... نحن أخوان
We used to sleep together like this all the time.
كنّا ننام هكذا معاً طوال الوقت
Y-Yes, of course!
!أ-أجل، بالطبع
U-Uh, hello? Alice is your little sister.
مهلاً. آليس هي أختك الصّغيرة
There's no way... my LP would go up...
...مُحال أن... ترتفع نقاط حياتي
Why?
لماذا؟
Next time, "The Future of This Harem."
"الحلقة القادمة، "مستقبل فعاليّة النساء هذه
#05 "The Future of This Harem"
"الحلقة 5  "مستقبل فعاليّة النساء هذه
Illustration: Fuumi
الرّسم: فومي